delivra.net 2009-05-18

# Privacy Policy | Delivra

At Delivra, we take your privacy seriously. Ours is a reputation business and it's critical to our success (and the success of our clients), that we make privacy a cornerstone of our operations. The bottom line is that we'll never use the information you entrust to us for purposes other than that information's intended use. Common sense and honesty are fundamental values here at Delivra, and we welcome your questions and comments about this important issue. Use the Contact Us page to quickly get in touch with us.

Information security permeates our organization. All Delivra staff are trained and undergo periodic refreshers in Information Security. View our Information Security policy for specifics. It's worth specifically noting here that we do have infrastructure partners that have limited access to some Delivra systems. Any partner or contractor that may come into contact with any Delivra data signs a non-disclosure agreement and only has access for the purposes of troubleshooting or administration of computer equipment. That access is on an as-needed basis and only for the appropriate time period necessary. We strictly monitor all access and our Security Officer is always available to answer questions or respond to concerns. Use the Contact Us page to quickly get in touch with the Security Officer.

#### Delivra's stance on SPAM

We follow a strict anti-SPAM policy here at Delivra. View our anti-SPAM policy for specifics. We send "permission based" or "opt-in" email ONLY. You can always report suspected abuses of this policy to [abuse@delivra.com](mailto:abuse@delivra.com "Send e-mail to abuse@delivra.com").

#### Opting out

Every message sent from Delivra software contains a link that allows the recipient to "opt-out" of receiving future email messages from that sender. Use the link in the footer of the email message or forward the entire message to [abuse@delivra.com](mailto:abuse@delivra.com "Send e-mail to abuse@delivra.com").

#### Email sent to Delivra

When you submit an email message to Delivra, we may store your name, email address, and other information from the header of the email for future reference. We'll never sell or rent your email address, or any other personal information, with anyone except those specifically mentioned in this policy (see the Privacy Infrastructure section above for more).

#### Form submissions

Some of the forms Delivra uses request personal information. Again, we don't rent, sell, or share your information with anyone not specifically mentioned in this Privacy Policy. The information collected on the forms is used for the purposes spelled out on the form. We don't ever release that information to third parties.

#### If you send email using our systems

Our clients trust us with the precious commodity of their reputations by storing information about their members on our servers in the form of membership lists. View our Information Security topic for specifics on how seriously we take this trust. We will never sell, rent, lease, share, transfer or otherwise disclose that information (or list administrator login information) to third parties.

#### Automatic collection of data

Delivra utilizes "pixel tags" and other methods to report on the engagement of recipients of the emails we send to users of our software, as well as the recipients of emails sent by our clients. Pixel tags are small image files included in HTML emails. When a recipient's email client displays images, the image is retrieved from Delivra's servers, allowing our system to record data such as which email address opened the mailing. Collected data also includes the data and time, and other information used to analyze the delivery success and engagement of the recipient.

Delivra also logs all use of Delivra software in order to gauge traffic, troubleshoot problems, and analyze trends: which allow us to provide the quality service our clients expect.

Delivra utilizes cookies in order to deliver content specific to Web site visitor's interests and to improve the convenience and efficiency of our clients' experience when using our services. Usage of a cookie is not linked to any personally identifiable information in Delivra's products and email messages. Visitors can choose not to accept cookies, but doing so may inhibit use of Delivra's products and services.

#### Links to other Web sites

Delivra's Web site, and emails delivered through our software may include links to other Web sites. Delivra is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other Web sites.

#### Further questions

If you have any questions about Delivra's Privacy Policy, please contact us at 317-915-9400 or send us an email.
